<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RecyclerView</string>

    <string name="turkey_sports">Although soccer is the most popular sport in Turkey, basketball, volleyball, handball, track-and-field and wrestling
        (which is considered as the ancestral sport) are also popular. Furthermore, important international successes have been attained in weightlifting,
        boxing, tae-kwon-do, judo and archery in recent years.
    </string>

    <string name="us_sports">Based on revenue, the five major professional sports leagues in the United States are Major League Baseball (MLB),
        the National Basketball Association (NBA), the National Football League (NFL), Major League Soccer (MLS) and the National Hockey League (NHL).
    </string>

    <string name="italy_sports">Sport in Italy has a long tradition. In several sports, both individual and team, Italy has good representation and many successes.
        Football is the most popular sport in Italy. Italy won the 2006 FIFA World Cup, and is (along with Germany) currently the second most successful football
        team in World Cup history, after Brazil, having won four FIFA World Cup championships.
        Basketball, volleyball, and cycling are the next most popular/played sports, with Italy having a rich tradition in all three. Italy also has strong
        traditions in swimming, water polo, rugby union, tennis, athletics, fencing and Formula One.
    </string>

    <string name="spain_sports">Sport in Spain in the second half of the 20th century has always been dominated by football. Other popular sport activities
        include basketball, tennis, cycling, handball, motorcycling, Judo, Formula One, water sports, rhythmic gymnastics, golf and skiing. Spain has also hosted
        a number of international events such as the 1992 Summer Olympics in Barcelona and the 1982 FIFA World Cup.
    </string>

    <string name="portugal_sports">Sports in Portugal are important in Portuguese culture. Football is the most popular sport in Portugal. Other than football,
        many other professional or semi-professional well organized sport competitions take place every season in Portugal, including basketball, swimming,
        athletics, tennis, gymnastics, futsal, rink hockey, team handball, volleyball, surfing, canoeing and rugby union championships among the hundreds of
        sports played in this country.
    </string>



</resources>